Mostafa Sharaf



Details

Al Qudra Road, Town Square,
Reem, Unit 270
Dubai
United Arab Emirates
+971 58 564 0935
mostafamuhamedaly@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Egyptian

Links

Github

Linkedin

Skills

React

JavaScript

Git

Python

HTML

CSS

Java

Node.js

MongoDB

C#

Languages

Arabic

English

Profile

Frontend developer who is solution-focused and skilled at working in a team atmosphere. Demonstrated expertise with HTML, CSS, ReactJS, Figma Design and JavaScript to create consumer-focused websites. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer, Carbon Glance, United Kingdom (Remotely)

DECEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

Carbon Glance is a dynamic startup dedicated to simplifying the compliance process for industrial companies in Europe by generating CBAM (Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism) reports. Developed and maintained the user interface for the CBAM report generation platform. Created clean, intuitive, and user-friendly designs to enhance the overall user experience (UX/UI). Ensured high performance and responsiveness of the web application. Implemented form validations, handled some backend tasks, and applied CI/CD pipelines for repositories.

Frontend Developer, Venu.ai, Cairo

SEPTEMBER 2022 - OCTOBER 2023

Worked as a frontend developer using React and a UX/UI designer using Figma. Was responsible for developing the client-side functionalities of a venue booking web application while also designing visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces. Collaborated with a multidisciplinary team, Integrated backend APIs, conducted research, created wireframes, and iteratively refined designs through feedback.

Frontend Developer Intern, Tutoruu, Cairo

APRIL 2022 - JULY 2022

Had the opportunity to gain valuable hands-on experience in web development while working with cutting-edge technologies. Played a pivotal role in crafting user-friendly and visually appealing interfaces using Vue.js and Tailwind CSS. Took on the additional responsibility of enhancing the user experience (UX).

Education

B.S. Computer Engineering, German University in Cairo, New Cairo

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JULY 2023

IGCSE, Egypt British International School, New Cairo

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2018

Freelance Projects

Linked Website, United States of America (Remotely)

OCTOBER 2023 — PRESENT

The hub showcases their projects, facilitates remote collaboration, and simplifies talent recruitment. With a user-friendly dashboard and an interactive blog, it's a dynamic space for creative collaboration and talent acquisition.